Mss.SMs.Coll.13
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Graphic Materials, 1906 - 1908; 1.0 box 2 photobooks (315 photographs)
  - "P.C.1206R", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "P.C.1205R", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "P.C.1200", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "P.C.1203R", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "P.C.1201R", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The CN Yards, 1908", 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "On Mile 114 July '07", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Us", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Yen - Yonos", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Draughting Room, Residency 49", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Residency 49, Camp No. 1", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "T. M. Baiyd, Div. Eng., J. A. Collins, Res., and Ogden, Chief Clerk", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Trinity", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Residency 49 in the Valley Camp", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Valley Camp", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Laying Temporary Tracks for Transportation of Equiptment", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The First Steel (temporary tracks)", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Toton Bucyrus Steam Shovel at Work", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Train Loading Up at Shovel Pit", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Big Fill, The Lower Deck", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Big Fill, December '07", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Circular Plough Grader", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "12 o'clock", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Taking Out a Cut with Traps", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Dump Train at Work", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Widening the First Lift", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Steam Shovel Dreging Sand for Cement Mixers", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Gravel Bar Saskalche", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "War River Bridge", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Top Deck, the Big Fill", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Clover Bar, Piers 10 and 11", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Stroud Grader at Work, Mile 116", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Two Machines at Work in One Cut, Cuts 200' wide, Mile 4", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "An Important Engineering Problem", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Steel Cars for the Bridge", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "70 Ton Crane at Work", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The First Steel, Pier 20 to 18", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Piers 15 and 14 from the Pumping Station", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Buff, Berger, and Milly", 1907; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Clover Bar, Sept. '08", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Saskatchewan Bridge, Clover Bar", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Pier 10, Clover Bar", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Steel of Pier 12", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "At Work on the Crown of the Big Fill", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Steam Shovel Loading Ballast", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Winterburn Lake", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "240,000 Ties at the Material Yards", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Residency 49, August '08", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Bunch", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Valley of Peace", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Finish of the Big Fill", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "In the Horse Lines at Stoney Plains", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "In the Horse Lines at Stoney Plains", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "At Stoney Plains", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "At Stoney Plains", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Eastern Slopes, Feb. '08", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Eastern Slopes, March '08", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Tie Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Moose", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Photographs.; Wild animals
  - "Bear", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "More Bear", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "On the Pombina", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Crossing the Athabasca", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The McLeod", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Rapids", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Silent Places, Prize Picture", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Ready", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "In the Yellowhead Valley", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "In the Yellowhead Valley", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Pine Pass", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Dog Trains From Great Slave Lakes", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Dog teams--Canada--1890-1920.; Photographs.; Railroads--Canada.
  - "Dog Trains From Great Slave Lakes", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Cache at Hudsons Hope", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Lodging at the Athabasca", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The National Transcontinental (Grand Trunk Pacific) Division of the West: Divivsion 3, Saskatchewan", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "W. H. Mitchell's Party at Dinorwic", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "W. H. Mitchell's Party and Branch Line", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Little Clean Up in the Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Rocky Lake, Macfarlens Portage", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Each of 'em doing his Country's Work, Drawing Dry Wood into Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Pete FinLayson and Train 4, "Evelyn" leader", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Bean Slinger", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Pride of the 7th Division, 95 Miles in 14 Hours", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Dog teams--Canada--1890-1920.; Photographs.
  - "Pisgou (leader), Red, Batard, and Smiler", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Glacier Ice", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "MG., NJ., A McD and JM.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Men of Party 6", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Tomorrow will be Friday", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Fishing Through Ice on Star Lake", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Train of the Transport Dept.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Building the Shacks at Headqts", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Ojibway Brat Fishing Through Hole in Ice", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A bunch of Party 6 Bow-wows", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Residency 29", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Residency 29", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Residency 13", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Draughting Room, Resdy. 13", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Authentic case of GM and JL caught working", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Ojibway Graves", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "No. 2 Train Party 6", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Effects of a Blizzard", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Hawk Lake Winter Trail", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Our Babies", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Bob, Haggerty", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Across Bad Ice", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Across Bad Ice", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "N.L.J. with Cip, Snapper, and Miner", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Devil's Head Caribou Lake", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Party 6 on "The Camp" Portage", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Dog Train on Sisiginigee", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Crack Team: Anamoose (leader), Mohegen, Coyote Jane, Coolee and Kawaee", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "An Ojibway Papoose", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Chief Handorgan", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Indians of North America; Photographs.
  - "Old Joe", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Packing", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The "Break Up" Snake River", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Little Christmas Decoration", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Rocky Lake", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Rocky Lake", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Rocky Lake Scaling Party", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Rocky Lake", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Dolles Rapids, Winnepeg River", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Party 3 on the Winnepeg", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Peggy Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Timber!", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Indian Birch Barks on the Winnepeg River", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Winnepeg River", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Winnipeg River", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Lac Seul", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Lac Seul", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Lake Abitibi", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "On the English River", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "R.M. Father Xmas", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "E.R Millidgece", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Canyon Lake Cache", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "J.A.M.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Joe KaeKwitch", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Ojibway Tepee", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Party 2", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Party 5", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Grandview Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Grandview Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Camp of the 1000 Lakes", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Bullpen", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "NJ.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "HP.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "BA.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Last Move", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Last Move", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Mermaids NJ and KK", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Mermaids NJ and KK", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Mermaids NJ and KK", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Big Game Hunting in Sask.", 1908
  - "Sunday", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Appears to be a cyanotype of "Sunday," APSdigobj_9272.
  - "Resdy. 21", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Resdy 21", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "KK", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Elm Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "King Muskawken, Senior Chief, Confederation of the Western Nations", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Muskowken, his sons, his daughter-in-law, and grandchildren", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Tepee", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Tents of Ishmael", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Blackfeet", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Chief Bullhorn Blackfeet", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Cree Squaws", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Surteau Family", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Cree Indians", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Sioux Braves", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "An Indian Sweat Bath", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Sioux Tepee", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Crees and Blackfeet", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Sioux", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "NoKomis (Grandmother)", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Listening to the address of the Indian Agent", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Racing at the Kutawa on the Birthday of the Great White Mother", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Racing at Kutawa on the Birthday of the Great White Mother", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "An Old Timer, a relic of '79", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Chief Wingard in Full Dress", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Sioux, Cree, Blackfeet, and Bloods", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Trooper of Police", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Stony Tepees", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Cree Brave and Squaw", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Cree Brave and Squaw", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Stonies", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Teepees in the Last Mountain Valley", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "In the Trail of the Mound Builder and the Buffalo", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Wa-wa-taysee", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "JRJ", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Handy Man", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Party of 5, yes also Moses", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Appears to be the same image as "French exercises," APSdigobj_9271.
  - "D Line Prelim", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Reversion to Type, JRT", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Mr. Dennis, Div. Engr.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "NJ earning his bread by the sweat of his brow", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "CWC Cooks, No. 1 Horse Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "WHT and HP.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "R.L.A.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "FR., AN., JT. and BN.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "BA, HP, HH, NJ, and WHT et Rags", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "WHT", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The First Snow", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Sunny Jims Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Herb and Teams", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "L Line", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Base Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Grub", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Grub", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Among the Big Timber", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "H Line Prelim", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Hayes and Morse", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Rags and Whitewash", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Supplies for the Locating Parties, Northern Sask", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Do You Keep Sugar?", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Mr. W.H. Tabeyee", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "P.S.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "R.F.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Home Sweet Home", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Appears to be the same image as "My side of the tent," APSdigobj_9274.
  - "Home Sweet Home", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "W.H.T.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Lac Montreal District, Northern Sask", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Lac Montreal District, Northern Sask.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Lac Montreal District Northern Sask.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Glimpse of Eden", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Mr. Hoynes and Mr. Morse", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "W.H.T.", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Habitant Guides Party 7 Location", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "HB and LC", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Hole Dug by Coyote, 8' deep, 28' long", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Muskowkan L R, Residency 22 and 23", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Muskowkan L R, Residency 22 and 23", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "B. MacKenzie, Factor, HB Post Touchwood", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Saskatchewan Derby, May 24", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "At Birch Lake Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Appears to be the same image as "How the camp is made artistic...", APSdigobj_9275.
  - "At Birch Lake Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "At Birch Lake Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Trooper, RNWMP, Kutawa", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "HB Post, Touchwood Hills", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Old Jesuit Mission at Touchwood", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "The Race Meeting at Kutawa, May 24", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Photograph of Lightning at Night on Praerie, 8 sec exposure", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Level Party on Resdy 23", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "50 Ton Steam Shovel, East of Saskatoon", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Work Train Going Down to Gravel Pit", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Mule Camp No. 1, Resdy 22", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Slushing", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Filling a Dump From 4 Borrow Pits, 2400ft Maximum Grade", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Dump Wagon Emptying", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Austen Grader at Mule Camp No. 2, Resdy 22", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Oxen Ditching", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Accident on the Dump, Hauling the Mules Out of the Water", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Lipton", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Base of Supplies", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "CWC Teamsters at Lipton", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Killing Meat for the Contract Camps", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Cuts and a 45ft Fill", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Cuts and a 45ft Fill", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Cuts and a 45ft Fill", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Ditching for Drainage with Oxen, Resdy 22", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Filling at No. 2 Horse Camp", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "16 Arch Cement Culvert", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "NJ Inspecting 4x4 Cedar Box Culverts", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Typical Praerie Fill Overhauling From a Cut", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "At No. 1 Horse Camp, Resdy 21", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "At No. 1 Horse Camp, Resdy 21", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Bridging at Saskatoon and Nutana", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Bridging at Saskatoon and Nutana", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Bridging at Saskatoon and Nutana", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "891 ft Trestle 1,500,000ft Lumber on Resdy 26", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "14 Arch Cement Culvert", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Wheelers at Work on Cut and Fill, Resdy 21", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Wheelers at Work on Cut and Fill, Resdy 21", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Filling Through Sloughs", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Snatch Teams", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "Filling Through Sloughs", 1908; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - Portrait, with wagon, undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Housed with Series I.
  - "Surto braves watch us pitch camp", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Housed with Series I. Appears to be the same image as "Cree Braves," APSdigobj9273.
  - Reading on a camp cot, 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "French exercises", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Appears to be the same image as "A Party of 5, yes also Moses," APSdigobj9122.
  - "Sunday", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Appears to be the same image as the cyanotype "Sunday," APSdigobj9086.
  - "Cree Braves", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Housed with Series I. Appears to be the same image as "Surto braves watch us pitch camp," APSdigobj9269.
  - "My side of the tent", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Housed with Series I. Appears to be the same image as "Home Sweet Home," APSdigobj9149.
  - "How the camp is made artistic...", 1906; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Housed with Series I. Appears to be the same image as "At Birch Lake Camp," APSdigobj9165.
  - Portrait of five, undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - Coyote in the street, undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Frontier and pioneer life -- Canada.; Photographs.; Wild animals
  - "Tom, Jerry and Barney", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - "A Crack Dog Team Party 6 7th Division N.T.C.R.", undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
  - Portrait of two, undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)
    Photographs.
  - Portrait, with trees, undated; 1.0 Photograph(s)